const quizDB = [
    {
        question: "Q1: What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello World' in Python?",
        a: 'echo "Hello World"',
        b: 'print("Hello World)"',
        c: 'echo("Hello World)"',
        d: 'p("Hello World)"',
        ans: "ans2"

    },

    {
        question: "Q2: How do you insert COMMENTS in Python code?",
        a: '//This is a comment',
        b: '#This is a Comment',
        c: '/*This is a Comment*/',
        d: '**This is a Comment',
        ans: 'ans2'

    },

    {
        question: "Q3: Which one is NOT a legal variable name?",
        a: "my-var",
        b: "Myvar",
        c: "my_var",
        d: '_myvar',
        ans: 'ans1'
    },

    {
        question: "Q4: How Do You create a variable with numberic Value 5?",
        a: "x = int(5)",
        b: "Both the Other answers are correct",
        c: "x=5",
        d: "None Of Given Options",
        ans: "ans2"
    },

    {
        question: "Q5: What is the correct file extension for Python files?",
        a: ".pt",
        b: ".py",
        c: ".pyth",
        d: ".pyt",
        ans: "ans2"
    },

    {
        question: "Q6: What is the correct syntax to output the type of a variable or object in Python?",
        a: "print(typeOf(x))",
        b: "print(typeof(x))",
        c: "print(tyof x)",
        d: "print(type(x))",
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q7: What is the correct syntax to return the first character in a string?",
        a: "function myFunction()",
        b: "def myFunction()",
        c: "create myFunction()",
        d: "func myFunction()",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q8: What is the correct way to create a function in Python?",
        a: 'x = sub("Hello", 0, 1)',
        b: 'x = "Hello"[0]',
        c: 'x = "Hello".sub(0,1)',
        d: "None of the given Options",
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q9: Which method can be used to remove any whitespace from both the beginning and the end of a string?",
        a: 'ptrim()',
        b: 'strip()',
        c: 'trim()',
        d: "len()",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q10: Which method can be used to replace parts of a string?",
        a: 'replaceString()',
        b: 'switch()',
        c: 'replace()',
        d: "repl()",
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q11: Which of these collections defines a LIST?",
        a: '{"apple","banana","cherry"}',
        b: '["apple","banana","cherry"]',
        c: '{"name":"apple","color":"green"}',
        d: '("apple";"banana";"cherry")',
        ans: "ans2"
    },
    {
        question: "Q12: Which of these collections defines a tuple?",
        a: '{"apple","banana","cherry"}',
        b: '["apple","banana","cherry"]',
        c: '{"name":"apple","color":"green"}',
        d: '("apple";"banana";"cherry")',
        ans: "ans4"
    },
    {
        question: "Q13: Which of these collections defines a DICTIONARY?",
        a: '{"apple","banana","cherry"}',
        b: '["apple","banana","cherry"]',
        c: '{"name":"apple","color":"green"}',
        d: '("apple";"banana";"cherry")',
        ans: "ans3"
    },
    {
        question: "Q13: Which collection is ordered, changeable, and allows duplicate members?",
        a: 'List',
        b: 'Dictionary',
        c: 'tuple',
        d: 'sets',
        ans: "ans1"
    },
    {
        question: "Q14: Which collection doesn't allow duplicate members?",
        a: 'List',
        b: 'Dictionary',
        c: 'tuple',
        d: 'sets',
        ans: "ans4"
    },
]

